SPOOKY IN LOVE
EPISODE 11
CEO KANG MIN-HWAN
SUBJECT: MA GANG-UK
SPECIAL NOTES
HISTORY OF HEART TRANSPLANT SURGERY
PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
PHONE, FAVORITES
102♥
DUJJIM
COLD CASE UNIT
PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
INTERNAL INVESTIGATION REPORT
ON REINA HOTEL CASE
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
INTERNAL PUBLIC INTEREST REPORT:
MISCONDUCT OF CORRUPT PUBLIC OFFICIALS
DISTRICT CHIEF PROSECUTOR MIN CHUNG-SEOK
VIDEO RECORDING CONSENT FORM
I HEREBY CONSENT
TO THE VIDEO RECORDING
OF MY STATEMENT
AND THE ENTIRE INTERVIEW PROCESS
WHILE APPEARING
AS A WITNESS
IN THE CASE
INVOLVING SUSPECT KIM SO-HUI
MAY 29, 2026
KIM SO-HUI
ASSEMBLYMAN PARK JIN-DONG,
SUBJECT TO ARREST WARRANT,
FOUND DEAD IN DISTRICT OFFICE
A COMPETENT WORKER!
PARK JIN-DONG
PERSONNEL TRANSFER NOTICE
NAME AND POSITION: PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
TRANSFERRED TO:
GYEONGSANGBUK-DO PROSECUTORS' OFFICE,
ANDONG BRANCH, CRIMINAL DEPARTMENT 1
GANG-UK
INCOMING CALL
PLEASE CHECK YOUR TEMPERATURE
BEFORE ENTERING
CORRECTIONAL SERVICES ADVANCING THE FUTURE
BY BALANCING ORDER AND HUMAN RIGHTS
DAESAN DETENTION CENTER
PARK SEUNG-JAE CLAIMS FIRST WIN
OF THE SEASON…
A DRAMATIC LAST-MINUTE TURNAROUND
NATIONAL MIDDLE AND HIGH SCHOOL
GOLF TOURNAMENT, WINNER
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
DETECTIVE
POLICE
VICE PRESIDENT SONG HUI-WON
INCOMING CALL
CHEON YEO-RI
COME MEET ME HERE
DO NOT ENTER
POLICE LINE
INVESTIGATION IN PROGRESS
SPOOKY IN LOVE